fast forward
Good Morning
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
I'm completely late.
I've been asked to meet late.
We're supposed to meet at 11:30.
But I woke up just in time to leave the house.
I woke up at the time I left home, so the meeting was returned at 12 o'clock.
seinen
ana
Thank you for watching!
one and a half and one and a half
Hi!
Today
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go
It's hot today.
I'll check it out.
Okay.
We're on our way.
Hey, subchan.
I'm on foot now. Ceri, the camera's taking pictures.
I can see it from here.
If we go straight this way, we'll be there. We're planning to go to two stores today.
One is a bakery Celica found for us, and the second one is near the bakery that sells cakes.
It got 4.3 stars on Tavelog.
Moa's was really expensive. Look up "Tsuchimachi-mae.
Moa's was the only one that came up.
I haven't been to Bakkatsu in a while. I was too busy to go in April.
So I'm going twice this month. It's the first time this month.
We're here early, Mr. Moa!
Let's go. I'm going inside the store.
I've made my choice. It really looks too good to be true.
As expected. Introducing the bread.
Serika chose these two.
Salted bread and cream doughnut!
They were so popular, weren't they?
She bought so many, and put them on her tray.
She couldn't stop, right?
They were buying an entire row of them. I thought they were delicious, so I bought them.
I saw that, and I bought them, too.
It's easy to be made into a movie. You know what I mean.
By the way, I just got these doughnuts.
This is the asparagus bread.
And this is rosemary bread.
I'll start with the savory one.
Yum.
Not white? Delicious.
It's sweet, too. Forget about it.
I should've asked for that. You want some?
This side.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it? It's good. It's good.
This is so good. I wish I could have had it.
It's good. It's really good.
It's really good!
I want everyone who likes oyster buns to try it.
Okay, Amiyu.
I'm going to buy it!
Rosemary
Looks so delicious!
I can smell the rosemary!
Let's go!
I'll go!
It's delicious.
Can you smell it?
It smells amazing.
Some kind of oil?
You dip it in olive oil, right?
It's a hokachu.
It's already got a lot of oil in it.
It's delicious with it.
Oh, my God.
Amazing!
Try it at home.
Yes, I'll try it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Delicious!
It's so good!
I'm going to take a bite of the doughnut, too.
I knew it. Everyone bought one.
Everybody was buying.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
It's amazing. It's got a lot of cream.
Yes, it is.
Can I eat it?
Can I show it to you?
See?
It's really delicious.
How is the sticky type?
It's good. It's all the rage right now. If it's that kind of place.
Yes, they are. It's all the rage now, isn't it?
It was delicious.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
Well, I'll eat slowly.
Bye bye.
Sao subchan.
Yes. Thank you for the food.Yes, I am. Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
Next, we go to the cake store.
Yay!
I'm looking forward to it. It's about a 10 minute walk from here,
A walk.
I'm going for a walk.
I've eaten well.
A walk before the halfway point.
A walk before we go.
Okay, I'm going.
See you later.
Bye-bye.
I bought a cake.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
There's a store in the hotel.
Can I ask you to go with me?
Yes, ma'am.
My name is...
This way.
Jajajan.
You see that?
It's in the store.
There's a cake in the shop.
Ta-da! Here it is!
It's so stylish.
Hey! Too stylish.
Too stylish.
And the cakes were individually decorated with flowers and stuff.
Yes! That's right!
They had edible flowers on them. They were so cute.
That's right.
My mom and the manager are around here.
I bought some gifts for them.
I hope they enjoy it.
Okay.
It's over. It's over for today.
Aren't you early?
Hey, it's early already.
It went by so fast.
It's raining, isn't it?
I know, right?
I rented an umbrella.
Thank you, Helika.
Umbrella rental debut.
Debut?
Judgment.
I got it.
Isn't it great? It's cheaper than buying one at a convenience store.
That's amazing.
I'm so happy.
Oh, my gosh, I'm so glad.
We've been renting these revolutionary umbrellas for a while now.
Congratulations!
I'd like to get under the Helika umbrella. I'd like to get under it.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
This video is about the Japanese traditional traditions of the HERICA Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional
Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions of the Traditional Traditions